Bakish Panday

London, ON /(647) 770-2664 / bakishpanday1@gmail.com

PROFILE

Experienced Sales and Customer service perosn with a demonstrated history of working in the Hospitality and services industry. Intermediate skilled in language like C, C#, javascript, CSS, and Microsoft Office. Have knowledge of the excellent customer service, sequential and object-oriented programming. Recently worked as Restaurant Manager at Dosa House currently focused on Application Developer course at Trios College.

SALIENT SKILLS

- Can adapt to change in technology and environment.
- Fast learner
- Can work in a team, independent and under minimum supervision.
- Analytical and problem-solving skills.
- Flexible, energetic, able to work extended hours and different shifts.

EDUCATION

Application Developer Trios College, London, ON April 2020 - **expected Jun 2021**

M.A. Tourism Management with Internship University of West London, United Kingdom

Sep 2012 - Nov 2014

ACHIEVEMENT

- Represented as an advisor at the event of Nepal's Tourism Industry on Recovery Strategies after the Earthquake (June, 2015), UK (PATA)
- Best Player of the Tournament (2000), Chitwan Cricket Club

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Restaurant Manager at Dosa House

Dec 2016 - Dec 2019

Markham, ON, Canada

I worked at above mentioned company as Manager performing following task

- Resolve Customer Complaints and Issues
- Provide traning to the new staff member
- Manage the stock level and order promptly
- Maintaining the premises according to the food and hygine standard

Line Cook at Bhais Indian Eatery

Dec 2015 - Nov 2016

Richmond Hill, ON

I worked at above company as a Line Cook for 11 months performing following tasks

- Prepare the food according to the order
- Assist the chef to prepare the food
- Clean the food preparing area
- Sucessfully worked in very busy and pressure working environment

Public Relation Officer at So Asia Restaurant

Sep 2013 - Nov 2015

Camberly, United Kindgom

I worked at above company as a Public Relation Officer for 14 months performing following tasks

- Planning, Developing and Implementing Public Relation Strategies
- Liaising with organisation to promote the business
- Writing and Editing in-house magazines, social media and articles

VOLUNTEERING EXPERIENCE

Program Instructure - Ms Office Basis for Newcomer Women July 2016

Welcome Immigration, Richmond Hill, ON

Program Assistant - Ipad Classes for Newcomers Senior

Welcome Immigration, Richmond Hill, ON

June 2016

Reception Assistant March 2016

Richvale Community Centre, Richmond Hill, ON

Reception Assistant Jan 2016

Wave Pool Community Centre, Richmond Hill, ON